D. H. Baldwin Company Records
D. H. Baldwin Company Records
- Baldwin Piano Company
  - General records
    - Advertising
      - General & advertising cash #12, 1933, Oct. - 1936, April (Volume 244)
      - General & advertising cash #13, 1936, May - 1938, July (Volume 245)
    - Wholesale department
      - Wholesale ledger #2, (D.H.B. & CO), 1906-1907 (Volume 246)
      - Wholesale ledger #1, 1930, Oct. - 1931, Dec. (Volume 247)
      - Wholesale ledger #2, 1932, Jan. (Volume 248)
      - Wholesale ledger #3, 1932, Feb. - 1933, June (Volume 249)
      - Wholesale ledger #4, 1933, July - 1933, Dec. (Volume 250)
      - Wholesale ledger #5, 1934-1935 (Volume 251)
      - Wholesale lease cash #2, 1927, Nov. - 1928, Dec. (Volume 252)
    - Retail department
      - Radio retail and special stories ledger, 1930, Jan. - 1930, Sept. (Volume 253)
      - Retail ledger #1, 1930, Oct. - 1931, Dec. (Volume 254)
      - Retail ledger #2, 1932 (Volume 255)
      - Retail ledger #3, 1933 (Volume 256)
      - Retail ledger #4, 1934 (Volume 257)
      - Retail ledger #5, 1935 (Volume 258)
      - Retail ledger #6, 1936 (Volume 259)
      - Retail ledger #7, 1937 (Volume 260)
      - Retail ledger #8, 1938, Jan. - July (Volume 261)
    - Agents and dealers
      - Denver dealer's ledger #1, 1908-1909 (Volume 262)
      - Denver dealer's ledger #2, 1910-1914 (Volume 263)
      - Denver dealer's ledger #3, 1915-1917 (Volume 264)
      - Denver dealer's ledger #6, 1918-1919 (Volume 265)
      - Denver dealer's ledger #7, 1920-1921 (Volume 266)
      - Denver dealer's ledger #8, 1922-1923 (Volume 267)
      - Denver dealer's ledger #9, 1924-1925 (Volume 268)
      - Denver dealer's ledger #10, 1926-1927 (Volume 269)
      - Denver dealer's ledger #11, 1928-1930 (Volume 270)
      - Cincinnati dealer's ledger #7, 1918, Aug. - 1920, Sept. (Volume 271)
      - Cincinnati dealer's ledger #9, 1922, July - 1923, Dec. (Volume 272)
      - Cincinnati dealer's ledger #9a, 1922, July - 1923, Dec. (Volume 273)
      - Cincinnati dealer's ledger #10, 1924, Jan. - 1925, Oct. (Volume 274)
      - Cincinnati dealer's ledger #10a, 1924, Jan. - 1925, Oct. (Volume 275)
      - Indianapolis dealer's ledger, 1912, May - 1928, April (Volume 276)
      - St. Louis agency accounts, 1925, Sept. - 1929, March (Volume 277)
      - St. Louis contingent accounts, 1928, June - Oct. (Volume 278)
      - Cincinnati contingent commissions #12, 1923, Sept.-1925, June (Volume 279)
      - Cincinnati contingent commissions #13, 1923, Sept.- 1925, June (Volume 280)
      - Report on individual salesmen (all cities), 1941, Jan. - 1943, Dec. (Volume 281)
    - Phonographs
      - Chicago phonograph ledger, 1928-1929 (Volume 282)
      - Chicago phonograph cash book, 1927, Aug. - 1929, Dec. (Volume 283)
      - Chicago phonograph cash book, 1930, Jan. - Aug. (Volume 284)
      - Cincinnati phonograph ledger #1, 1919, Nov. - 1920, Oct. (Volume 285)
      - Cincinnati phonograph ledger #2, 1920, Nov. - 1922, Dec. (Volume 286)
      - Cincinnati phonograph ledger #3, 1923, Jan. - 1925, Dec. (Volume 287)
      - Cincinnati phonograph ledger #4, 1926, Jan. - 1929, April (Volume 288)
      - Cincinnati phonograph ledger #5, 1929, May - 1930, Sept. (Volume 289)
      - Cincinnati phonograph ledger #6, 1930, Oct. (Volume 290)
      - Cincinnati phonograph cash book #3, 1922, June - 1923, Nov. (Volume 291)
      - Cincinnati phonograph cash book #4, 1923, Dec. - 1925, Aug. (Volume 292)
      - Cincinnati phonograph cash book #5, 1925, Sept. - 1927, March (Volume 293)
      - Cincinnati phonograph cash book #9, 1927, April - 1928, Dec. (Volume 294)
      - Cincinnati phonograph cash book #10, 1928, Dec. - 1929, Dec. (Volume 295)
      - Cincinnati phonograph sales book, 1920, Dec. - 1925, Nov. (Volume 296)
      - Cincinnati phonograph sales book, 1925, Dec. - 1930, Sept. (Volume 297)
      - Dallas phono ledger, 1917, March - 1918, June (Volume 298)
      - Dallas phonograph ledger, 1919, Aug. - 1923, June (Volume 299)
      - Dallas phono journal, 1919, July - 1923, July (Volume 300)
      - Dallas phonograph cash book, 1920, Oct. - 1923, July (Volume 301)
      - Dallas phonograph sales book, 1919, Aug. - 1920, Dec. (Volume 302)
      - Denver phonograph cash book, 1919, April - 1920, Sept. (Volume 303)
      - Denver phonograph cash book, 1922, March - 1924, Jan. (Volume 304)
      - Denver phonograph cash book, 1924, Feb. - 1925, Dec. (Volume 305)
      - Denver phonograph cash book, 1926, Jan. - 1927, Nov. (Volume 306)
      - Denver phonograph cash book, 1927, Dec. - 1929, Nov. (Volume 307)
      - Denver phonograph cash book, 1929, Dec. - 1931, July (Volume 308)
      - Louisville phonograph ledger, 1929, Jan. - 1930, Sept. (Volume 309)
      - Louisville phonograph sales book, 1927, Jan. - 1930, Sept. (Volume 310)
      - Indianapolis phonograph ledger, 1917, March - 1919, June (Volume 311)
      - Indianapolis phonograph ledger, 1921, Jan. - 1922, Dec. (Volume 312)
      - Indianapolis phonograph ledger, 1923, Jan. - 1925, June (Volume 313)
      - Indianapolis phonograph ledger, 1925, July - 1928, Dec. (Volume 314)
      - Indianapolis phonograph ledger, 1929, Jan. - Aug. (Volume 315)
      - Indianapolis phonograph cash book, 1922, Sept. - 1925, March (Volume 316)
      - Indianapolis phonograph cash book, 1925, April - 1927, April (Volume 317)
      - Indianapolis phonograph cash book, 1927, May - 1929, Aug. (Volume 318)
      - Indianapolis phonograph sales book, 1917, March - 1919, June (Volume 319)
      - Indianapolis phonograph sales book, 1925, June - 1929, Aug. (Volume 320)
      - St. Louis phonograph ledger #1, 1919, April - 1920, Dec. (Volume 321)
      - St. Louis phonograph ledger #2, 1921, Jan. - 1922, Dec. (Volume 322)
      - St. Louis phonograph ledger #3, 1923, Jan. - 1927, Dec. (Volume 323)
      - St. Louis phonograph ledger #4, 1928, Jan. - 1929, Dec. (Volume 324)
      - St. Louis phonograph ledger #5, 1930, Jan. - 1931, Dec. (Volume 325)
  - Division records
    - General
      - General ledger, 1928, Jan. - 1929, Sept. (Volume 326)
      - General ledger, 1929, Oct. - 1930, Sept. (Volume 327)
      - General ledger, 1930, Oct. - 1931, Oct. (Volume 328)
      - General journal, 1927, Aug. - 1928, June (Volume 329)
      - General journal, 1928, June - 1929, April (Volume 330)
      - General journal, 1929, April - 1930, March (Volume 331)
      - General journal, 1930, March - 1930, Sept. (Volume 332)
      - Cash book, 1926, Aug. - 1927, March (Volume 333)
      - Cash book, 1927, March - 1927, Nov. (Volume 334)
      - Cash book, 1927, Nov. - 1928, June (Volume 335)
      - Cash book, 1928, June - 1929, Jan. (Volume 336)
      - Cash book, 1928, Jan. - 1929, Dec. (Volume 337)
      - Cash book, 1929, Dec. - 1930, Aug. (Volume 338)
    - Cincinnati
      - Ledger #1, 1903, July - 1905, Sept. (Volume 339)
      - Ledger #2, 1905, Oct. - 1907, April (Volume 340)
      - Ledger #3, 1907, May - Dec. (Volume 341)
      - Ledger #1, 1908, Jan. - 1909, Dec. (Volume 342)
      - Ledger #2, 1910, Jan. - 1911, March (Volume 343)
      - Ledger #3, 1912, April - 1913, Dec. (Volume 344)
      - Ledger #4, 1914, Jan. - 1916, June (Volume 345)
      - Ledger #5, 1916, July - 1918, July (Volume 346)
      - Ledger #7, 1920, Oct. - 1922, June (Volume 347)
      - Ledger #8, 1922, July - 1924, March (Volume 348)
      - Ledger #9, 1924, April - 1925, Oct. (Volume 349)
      - Ledger #10, 1925, Nov. - 1927, June (Volume 350)
      - Ledger #11, 1927, July - 1929, April (Volume 351)
      - Ledger #12, 1929, May - 1930, Aug. (Volume 352)
      - Ledger #13, 1930, Sept. (Volume 353)
      - Cash book #1, 1908, Jan. - Sept. (Volume 354)
      - Cash book #5, 1910, Oct. - 1911, May (Volume 355)
      - Cash book #6, 1911, June - 1912, Jan. (Volume 356)
      - Cash book #7, 1912, Feb. - Sept. (Volume 357)
      - Cash book #8, 1912, Oct. - 1913, May (Volume 358)
      - Cash book #9, 1913, June - 1914, Jan. (Volume 359)
      - Cash book #10, 1914, Feb. - Sept. (Volume 360)
      - Cash book #11, 1914, Oct. - 1915, May (Volume 361)
      - Cash book #12, 1915, June - Dec. (Volume 362)
      - Cash book #13, 1916, Jan. - Aug. (Volume 363)
      - Cash book #15, 1917, April - Nov. (Volume 364)
      - Cash book #16, 1917, Nov. - 1918, July (Volume 365)
      - Cash book #17, 1918, Aug. - 1919, March (Volume 366)
      - Cash book #18, 1919, March - Nov. (Volume 367)
      - Cash book #19, 1919, Nov. - 1920, June (Volume 368)
      - Cash book #20, 1920, June - 1921, Feb. (Volume 369)
      - Cash book #21, 1921, Feb. - Sept. (Volume 370)
      - Cash book #22, 1921, Oct. - 1922, April (Volume 371)
      - Cash book #23, 1922, April - Nov. (Volume 372)
      - Cash book #24, 1922, Nov. - 1923, May (Volume 373)
      - Cash book #25, 1923, May - Nov. (Volume 374)
      - Cash book #26, 1923, Nov. - 1924, June (Volume 375)
      - Cash book #27, 1924, June - 1925, Jan. (Volume 376)
      - Cash book #28, 1925, Jan. - Aug. (Volume 377)
      - Cash book #29, 1925, Aug. - 1926, Feb. (Volume 378)
      - Cash book #30, 1926, Feb. - Aug. (Volume 379)
      - Cash book #31, 1926, Sept. - 1927, Feb. (Volume 380)
      - Cash book #32, 1927, Feb. - Aug. (Volume 381)
      - Cash book #33, 1927, Aug. - 1928, Feb. (Volume 382)
      - Cash book #34, 1928, March - Sept. (Volume 383)
      - Cash book #35, 1928, Sept. - 1929, April (Volume 384)
      - Cash book #36, 1929, May - Dec. (Volume 385)
      - Cash book Pages, 1933, Jan. - Dec. (Volume 386)
      - Cash book Pages, 1934, Jan. - Dec. (Volume 387)
      - Cash book Pages, 1938, Feb. (Volume 388)
      - Sales record, 1919, April - 1920, Oct. (Volume 389)
      - Sales record, 1920, Nov. - 1922, Sept. (Volume 390)
      - Sales record, 1922, Oct. - 1924, Feb. (Volume 391)
      - Sales record, 1924, March - 1925, Sept. (Volume 392)
      - Sales record, 1925, Oct. - 1927, Feb. (Volume 393)
    - Dallas
      - Ledger #3, 1913, Feb. - 1915, Aug. (Volume 394)
      - Ledger #4, 1915, Sept. - 1917, Jan. (Volume 395)
      - Ledger #5, 1917, Feb. - 1918, Aug. (Volume 396)
      - Ledger #6, 1918, Sept. - 1920, Aug. (Volume 397)
      - Ledger #7, 1920, Sept. - 1922, Dec. (Volume 398)
      - Ledger #8, 1923, Jan. - 1924, June (Volume 399)
      - Ledger #9, 1924, July - 1925, Sept. (Volume 400)
      - Ledger #10, 1925, Oct. - 1927, March (Volume 401)
      - Ledger #11, 1927, April - 1929, Aug. (Volume 402)
      - Ledger #12, 1929, Sept. - 1931, Dec. (Volume 403)
      - Cash book, 1914, June - 1915, Oct. (Volume 404)
      - Cash book, 1915, Oct. - 1916, Dec. (Volume 405)
      - Cash book, 1916, Dec. - 1918, Jan. (Volume 406)
      - Cash book, 1918, Jan. - 1919, Jan. (Volume 407)
      - Cash book, 1919, Feb. - Nov. (Volume 408)
      - Cash book, 1919, Dec. - 1921, Jan. (Volume 409)
      - Cash book, 1921, Jan. - 1922, March (Volume 410)
      - Cash book, 1922, April - Dec. (Volume 411)
      - Cash book, 1923, Jan. - 1924, May (Volume 412)
      - Cash book, 1924, June - 1925, July (Volume 413)
      - Cash book, 1925, Aug. - 1926, Oct. (Volume 414)
      - Cash book, 1926, Nov. - 1928, Feb. (Volume 415)
      - Cash book, 1928, March - 1929, May (Volume 416)
      - Cash book, 1929, June - 1931, Dec. (Volume 417)
      - Sales record, 1916, July - 1920, March (Volume 418)
      - Sales record, 1920, April - 1923, June (Volume 419)
      - Sales record, 1923, July - 1925, June (Volume 420)
      - Sales record, 1925, July - 1927, June (Volume 421)
      - Sales record, 1927, July - 1929, Jan. (Volume 422)
    - Denver
      - Ledger, 1903, Jan. - June (Volume 423)
      - Ledger #1, 1903, July - 1907, Aug. (Volume 424)
      - Ledger #2, 1907, Sept. - Dec. (Volume 425)
      - General ledger #2, 1908-1909 (Volume 426)
      - General ledger #3, 1910, Jan. - 1913, June (Volume 427)
      - General ledger #4, 1913, July - 1915, Dec. (Volume 428)
      - General ledger #5, 1916-1917 (Volume 429)
      - General ledger #6, 1918-1919 (Volume 430)
      - General ledger #7, 1920-1921 (Volume 431)
      - General ledger #8, 1922-1923 (Volume 432)
      - General ledger #9, 1924-1925 (Volume 433)
      - General ledger #10, 1926-1927 (Volume 434)
      - General ledger #11, 1928-1929 (Volume 435)
      - General ledger #12, 1930-1931 (Volume 436)
      - Cash book, 1903, Feb. - July (Volume 437)
      - Cash book, 1903, July - 1906, June (Volume 438)
      - Cash book, 1906, July - 1907, Dec. (Volume 439)
      - Cash book, 1908 (Volume 440)
      - Cash book, 1909 (Volume 440a)
      - Cash book, 1910 (Volume 441)
      - Cash book, 1911 (Volume 442)
      - Cash book, 1912, Jan. - Nov. (Volume 443)
      - Cash book, 1912, Nov. - 1913, Aug. (Volume 444)
      - Cash book, 1913, Sept. - 1914, May (Volume 445)
      - Cash book, 1914, June - 1915, Jan. (Volume 446)
      - Cash book, 1915, Feb. - Sept. (Volume 447)
      - Cash book, 1915, Oct. - 1916, June (Volume 448)
      - Cash book, 1916, July - 1917, April (Volume 449)
      - Cash book, 1917, May - Dec. (Volume 450)
      - Cash book, 1918, Jan. - June (Volume 451)
      - Cash book, 1918, July - 1919, June (Volume 452)
      - Cash book, 1919, July - 1920, Feb. (Volume 453)
      - Cash book, 1920, March - Sept. (Volume 454)
      - Cash book, 1920, Oct. - 1921, April (Volume 455)
      - Cash book, 1921, May - Nov. (Volume 456)
      - Cash book, 1921, Dec. - 1922, June (Volume 457)
      - Cash book, 1922, July - 1923, Jan. (Volume 458)
      - Cash book, 1923, Feb. - Sept. (Volume 459)
      - Cash book, 1923, Sept. - 1924, March (Volume 460)
      - Cash book, 1924, April - Oct. (Volume 461)
      - Cash book, 1924, Nov. - 1925, May (Volume 462)
      - Cash book, 1925, June - Dec. (Volume 463)
      - Cash book, 1926, Jan. - July (Volume 464)
      - Cash book, 1926, Aug. - 1927, Feb. (Volume 465)
      - Cash book, 1927, March - Sept. (Volume 466)
      - Cash book, 1927, Oct. - 1928, April (Volume 467)
      - Cash book, 1928, May - Oct. (Volume 468)
      - Cash book, 1928, Nov. - 1929, Nov. (Volume 469)
      - Cash book, 1929, Dec. - 1930, Dec. (Volume 470)
      - Cash book, 1931 (Volume 471)
      - Sales record, 1908, Jan. - 1911, Aug. (Volume 472)
      - Sales record, 1911, Sept. - 1914, Dec. (Volume 473)
      - Sales record, 1915-1917 (Volume 474)
      - Sales record, 1918, Jan. - 1920, June (Volume 475)
      - Sales record, 1920, July - 1922, Dec. (Volume 476)
      - Sales record, 1923-1924 (Volume 477)
      - Sales record, 1925-1926 (Volume 478)
      - Sales record, 1927-1928 (Volume 479)
      - Sales record, 1929, Jan. - March (Volume 480)
    - Detroit
      - Ledger, 1923, Jan. - 1925, June (Volume 481)
      - Ledger, 1929, Sept. - Dec. (Volume 482)
    - Eastern
      - Ledger, 1915, Jan. - 1916, June (Volume 483)
      - Ledger, 1927, Jan. - 1930, Sept. (Volume 484)
      - Cash book, 1929, July - 1930, Sept. (Volume 485)
      - Sales record, 1926, Dec. - 1929, Feb. (Volume 486)
    - Indianapolis
      - Ledger, 1917, Jan. - 1919, June (Volume 487)
      - Ledger, 1919, July - 1922, Dec. (Volume 488)
      - Ledger, 1925, July - 1926, Dec. (Volume 489)
      - Ledger, 1927, Jan. - 1928, Dec. (Volume 490)
      - Ledger, 1929, Jan. - Aug. (Volume 491)
      - Cash book, 1924, Sept. - 1925, Sept. (Volume 492)
      - Cash book, 1925, Oct. - 1926, Oct. (Volume 493)
      - Cash book, 1926, Nov. - 1927, Dec. (Volume 494)
      - Cash book, 1927, Dec. - 1929, Jan. (Volume 495)
      - Cash book, 1929, Feb. - Dec. (Volume 496)
      - Sales record, 1918, July - 1919, June (Volume 497)
      - Sales record, 1919, July - 1922, June (Volume 498)
      - Sales record, 1922, July - 1924, Sept. (Volume 499)
      - Sales record, 1924, Oct. - 1926, Aug. (Volume 500)
      - Sales record, 1926, Sept. - 1928, March (Volume 501)
      - Sales record, 1928, April - 1929, March (Volume 502)
    - St. Louis
      - Ledger, 1926, Jan. - 1929, April (Volume 503)
      - Ledger, 1929, May - 1930, Sept. (Volume 504)
      - Cash book, 1929, Aug. - 1929, July (Volume 505)
      - Sales record, 1929, Jan. - Feb. (Volume 506)
    - Southern
      - Ledger, 1917, Jan. - 1918, June (Volume 507)
      - Ledger, 1918, July - 1921, June (Volume 508)
      - Ledger, 1927, July - 1928, Oct. (Volume 509)
      - Sales record, 1921, Sept. - 1924, Dec. (Volume 510)
    - Export
      - Ledger #4, 1916, June - 1918, Jan. (Volume 511)
      - Ledger #5, 1918, Jan. - 1922, Dec. (Volume 512)
      - Ledger #7, 1929, Jan. - 1938, July (Volume 513)
      - Journal #5, 1923, March - 1936, Dec. (Volume 514)
      - Cash book #5, 1920, Feb. - 1922, Nov. (Volume 515)
      - Cash book #6, 1922, Dec. - 1924, April (Volume 516)
      - Cash book #7, 1924, May - 1925, Aug. (Volume 517)
      - Cash book #8, 1925, Sept. - 1927, Jan. (Volume 518)
      - Cash book #9, 1927, Jan. - 1928, May (Volume 519)
      - Cash book, 1929, Sept. - 1931, March (Volume 520)
      - Cash book, 1931, April - 1938, July (Volume 521)
      - Sales record, 1915, Sept. - 1920, Sept. (Volume 522)
      - Sales record, 1920, Oct. - 1926, Aug. (Volume 523)
      - Sales record, 1926, Sept. - 1938, July (Volume 524)
- Miscellaneous records
  - Ledger, Ellington, Hamilton and Baldwin Manufacturing Company, 1930, Oct. - 1933, July (Volume 525)
  - Journal, 1914, Jan. - 1915, June (Volume 526)
  - Journal, 1916, Jan. - 1917, March (Volume 527)
  - Journal, 1917, Jan. - 1918, May (Volume 528)
  - Journal, 1917, April - 1919, June (Volume 529)
  - Journal, 1917, Oct. - 1919, Dec. (Volume 530)
  - Journal, 1919, July - 1922, Nov. (Volume 531)
  - Journal, 1920, Jan. - Dec. (Volume 532)
  - Journal, 1920, Oct. - 1924, Jan. (Volume 533)
  - Journal, 1922, Jan. - Dec. (Volume 534)
  - Journal, 1922, Dec. - 1925, July (Volume 535)
  - Journal, 1923, Jan. - 1923, Oct. (Volume 536)
  - Journal, 1923, Nov. - 1924, Nov. (Volume 537)
  - Journal, 1925, April - 1926, Feb. (Volume 538)
  - Journal, 1925, Aug. - 1926, Nov. (Volume 539)
  - Journal, 1925, Dec. - 1928, Jan. (Volume 540)
  - Journal, 1926, July - 1927, Sept. (Volume 541)
  - Journal, 1927, Jan. - Dec. (Volume 542)
  - Journal, 1929, April - Dec. (Volume 543)
  - Journal, 1929, Oct. - 1930, Aug. (Volume 544)
  - Journal, 1930, Jan. - Dec. (Volume 545)
  - Journal, 1930, July - 1931, Dec. (Volume 546)
  - Journal, 1930, July - 1932, April (Volume 547)
  - Journal, 1933, Sept. - 1934, Dec. (Volume 548)
  - Journal, 1935, Jan. - 1936, Dec. (Volume 549)
  - Journal, 1936, July - 1938, Jan. (Volume 550)
  - Journal, 1937, Jan. - 1938, Dec. (Volume 551)
  - Journal, 1938, Feb. - June (Volume 552)